Previously on chicago fire.
"风城烈焰"前情提要
You,are not taking my house.
你别想就这么接手我的消防队
Not without a fight.
我不会让你轻易得手的
Do you think i'm dating benny?
你以为我和Benny约会呢?
I'm his daughter katie.
我是他女儿 Katie
When i needed you most,you left.
我最需要你的时候 你离开了
I'm here to say i'm sorry.
我就是来道歉的
Hop in the back.
到后面坐
With all the eyes on this house,
这么多双眼睛盯着咱们队里
You really think it's a good idea to bring people on ridealongs?
你觉得让人跟着参观出任务合适吗?
What,i can't have a friend here?
干嘛 我带个朋友还不行么?
Help me.please!
救救我 求你了!
Flaco's dead.
Flaco死了
We'll take this to thegrave,just me and you.
我们都守口如瓶就好
You've always been there for me.
我需要你的时候 你总是陪着我
Yeah,that'll never change.
嗯 以后也一样
I promised heather i'd have this stuff boxed up and shipped by friday.
我答应Heather周五之内 把东西都打包好装运
You did a good job takingcare of those kids,matt.
Matt 你把孩子们照顾得很好
I'm gonna miss coming by andhanging out with those guys.
我会怀念过来和孩子们玩的时光的
You can still come by.
你还是可以过来玩的啊
I may not be as good at charades,but i can be decent company.
我可能比不上猜字游戏 但是和我消磨下时间还是不错的
all right,i think that's the last of it.
好了 这应该是最后一件了
I'm serious.You should still come by.
我认真的 有空就过来
What?
什么意思?
I. I just feel like we've already been downthis road,you know?
我只是觉得我们已经有前车之鉴了
Yeah.
嗯
I'll see you at work.
队里见了
Sure.
好
Kind of unfair that i have to pay rent and she doesn't.
她不付房租 我得付 有点不公平
Life is unfair,otis.
人生就是不公平的 Otis
There you go.
受着吧
Is that a viper helmet?
那是Viper头盔吗?
Yeah,yeah,yeah.Yes,yes,it is.
嗯 对 是的
You're a battlestar fan?
你是"太空堡垒"的粉丝?
This the dual signature edition,both hatch and benedict?
这是双签名版本的 Hatch和Benedict?
Yeah,i bought it forlike 350 a few years back,
嗯 我几年前350块买的
But it's worth way more than that now.
现在可升值不少
Better investment than stocks any day.
绝对比投资股票合适啊
That's exactly what i told my mom.
我就这么跟我妈说的
Morning.
早
We blowing off work today?
今天都不上班?
No
不是
i put in a transfer to another house.
我申请调到其他站了
You. You put in a transfer?
你申请调走?
What. What do you mean?
什么 什么意思?
I just wanted.i want a change of scenery.
我只是想换换环境
It's. It's getting stagnant there.
站里气氛太沉闷了
Okay.For how long?
好吧 去多久?
I. I'm. I'm not coming back to 51.
我没打算再回51号站
The tech professor was telling me about some jobs inheatingAnd cooling repair that
技工课的老师告诉我说 有些修理供冷供热系统的工作
pay real good money.
钱拿得不少
Good.As soon as you get yourdegree,you can look into it.
很好 等你拿到学位了 就着手找工作吧
Yes,boss.
遵命
Leon.
Leon
Yvette,be careful.
Yvette 小心点
Drive that thing like a kamikaze.
骑车跟敢死队一样
Girl hasn't listened to us since we babysat her.
这姑娘从小时候就没听过我们的话
Yo,i'ma call you after i get out of class.
我下课了给你打电话
Go,go,go!
走 走 走!
Yvette!
Yvette!
no,no,no.
不 不
- No,come on. - Joe,she's breathing?
- 不要啊 - Joe 她还有呼吸吗?
Come on.Come on,baby.
加油 坚持住
Joe?
Joe?
Come on!
坚持住啊!
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync: YTET-天外飞砖
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: Grace S 片风 西瓜 校对: 狄克森 时间轴: 天外飞砖
chicago.fire.208.
风城烈焰 第二季 第8集
Gunshot wound to the back of her neck.
颈后部中枪
I got her pulse back.
又有脉搏了
Get her into the ambulance,get her on a monitor.
抬上救护车 上监护仪
She's hanging on.
她应该没事
I don't need no damn doctors,man.
我才不要什么医生呢
Get the hell up off me!
别碰我!
Yo,that's dom.
那人是Dom
The insane kings beenafter him for a while.
疯狂魔王帮想对付他很久了
- Get out of here. - Why?Who's that?
- 你快走 - 为什么? 那人是谁?
Just go.
你先走
Recognized you from firehouse 51.
看出来你是51号消防站的了
Yeah.
嗯
Hank voight.Detective lindsay.
Hank Voight 这是Lindsay警探
Joe cruz.
Joe Cruz
Did you see what happened?
你看到事情经过了吗?
I was around the cornerwhen the shots were fired.
我在街角听到了枪声
I. Shooter's car wasgone by the time i ran up.
我跑过来的时候凶手已经开车走了
Yvette,the victim.She.
Yvette 受害人
I know her and her mom.
我认识她还有她妈妈
They're neighbors.
是我邻居
It's a terrible thing.I hope she's all right.
真不幸 希望她没事
Yeah,we'll see if we can get any i.d.on the shooter from witnesses.
我们去问问看 有没有目击者看清楚了凶手
I know where to find you.
我需要随时找你
- Sorry,man. - sorry.
- 真抱歉 - 抱歉
Excuse me,are you areallife firefighter?
不好意思 你真是消防员吗?
Isabella.is this your coffee spot?
Isabella 你也在这儿买咖啡?
I remember you used to get coffee here.
我记得你一直在这里买的
- I was hoping to run into you. - Okay.
- 过来想遇到你 - 好吧
i have to go to this blacktie eventtomorrow night for work.
我明晚工作需要 有很正式的晚会
Any chance you wanna join me?
你愿意和我一起去吗?
I'm dateless.
找不到别人了
I mean,i'd.I'd loveto,but i don't have a tux.
愿意是愿意 但是我没有礼服
I can get you one.
我给你弄一套
Come on,it'll be fun.I promise.
去吧 会很有意思的 我保证
Okay.
好吧
Benny sent me christmas presents almost every years,
Benny基本上每年都给我寄圣诞礼物
So i'll give him that.
这点做的还是不错的
Same here.Express mail.
也给我寄 还是快递优先件
So what's your real family like?
那你真正的家庭是如何的?
My mom got married when i was four,
我妈妈在我4岁的时候结婚了
and i have two stepsisters,Twins,volleyball champions of the world.
我有两个双胞胎继妹 世界排球冠军
- Cool. - Yeah.
- 不错啊 - 嗯
A lot of travel,though.
当然 总是到处跑
My mom and stepdad are attheir tournaments every weekend.
我妈和继父每周末 都去看她们的巡回赛
I'm sure they're proud of you too.
他们肯定也觉得你特棒
Yeah.
嗯
I don't plan on.On working here forever.
我没打算一直在这里干活
I'm hoping to start my owncatering company someday.
我希望某天可以开自己的餐饮服务公司
- That's great. - Yeah.
- 真好 - 对
So what got you into cooking?
你为什么对烹饪感兴趣呢?
Who knows?
我也说不清
I better get back to work,though.
我得回去干活了
Sure.
嗯
It's been a really weirdthing seeing benny again
再看到Benny其实蛮诡异的
And finding out about a halfsibling.
然后发现自己有半个哥哥
Little weird.
有点诡异
Well,it was. It was really nice meeting you,kelly.
不过 很高兴认识你 Kelly
Any chance you'd want to come by the firehouse and cook for us?
你有兴趣来消防队给我们做饭吗?
We'd supply all the ingredients.
食材都是我们准备
And it would be good practice for the catering gig.
算是给你练练手
Sure.That'd be great.
好啊 我很愿意
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 真的? - 嗯
- 6:00? - That's perfect.
- 6点? - 没问题
- Okay. - All right,i'll see you then.
- 好了 - 嗯 那到时候见了
And of course,you know,my mother's blaming me,
我妈当然是怪我了
Saying that as her employers,
说既然雇了她
We should have figured out a way to keep her in the country.
就应该想办法让她能留在美国
No offense,but zoya's english was a little no bueno.
没别的意思 但是Zoya的英语真的不咋地
It might boost sales if we got a bartender
如果我们的服务员能和客人有所沟通
Who could actually communicate with the customers.
也许生意能好起来
Zoya's leaving?
Zoya要走了?
- Yeah.
- 对
Back to mother russia.
回她祖国俄罗斯去了
Heard sergeant voightcalled here looking for you.
我听说Voight打电话来找你
What's that about?
怎么回事?
He's working a driveby went down in my neighborhood this morning.
他今早在我家附近负责一起 驾车开枪的案子
I was nearby when it happened.
案发的时候我就在附近
Morning,everybody.
大家早上好
I have a quick announcement to make.
我有个事情要通知一下
Shay has transferred out of 51.
Shay要调离51号站了
Transferred as in.As in like past tense?As in not coming back?
调动已经生效了? 她不打算回来了?
Correct,and it is her prerogative.
没错 是她自己的决定
Look,shay served this house well.
总的来说 Shay为消防队做了很多贡献
This here is alan choot.
这位是Alan Choot
He's gonna be working with us this shift.
以后他将与我们一起共事
Chout,actually.
其实 我叫Chout
Rhymes with shout.Great to meet you guys.
容易误听成Shout 很高兴认识大家
I am sure you will givehim a warm 51 welcome.
我相信大家会热烈欢迎他的到来的
You're dawson,right?
你是Dawson 对吧?
Yeah.
是的
Heard great things about you.
之前听说过很多有关你的事情
Glad to be here.Looking forward to seeing some action.
能来这真是太好了 希望今后合作愉快
did.Did you know about this?
喂 你之前听说这件事没?
I found out at 7:15 this morning.
今天早上我才知道的
Hello,wallace.
Wallace 你好啊
You reneged on a deal.
你出尔反尔
I changed my mind.
我改变主意了而已
It's within my rights to do so.
我有权这么做
You and i,we.We. We've had some disagreements in the past,
我们俩之前有些分歧
But that's to be expected.
那是意料之中的事情
And i think we played fair and were respectful of each other.
但至少我们还是相互尊重 照游戏规则来办事的
And i like my job when i'm working in a situation like that.
我觉得那种工作方式挺好的
But when someone crosses me or underestimates me,
但如果有人敢挑衅或者低估我
I like it even more
我会更加高兴
because it gives me an opportunity
因为那样我就有机会
To show exactly what i'm capable of.
展示我真正的能力了
Make no mistake.
千万别被我抓到把柄
I'm going to shut down 51.
否则我就让这个消防站关门
And when i'm done doing that,
等我把这个站关了
i'm gonna bury you.
接着就来收拾你
pouch,get back here.
Pouch 回来
Sorry about the busybody.
这家伙实在太好动了
No problem.Nice to meet you.
没关系的 你真可爱
Guys,this is my wife lisa.
伙计们 这位是我的妻子 Lisa
This is herrmann,otis,and mouch.
这几位是Herrmann Otis还有Mouch.
- Great to meet you,lisa. - Yeah,same here.
- Lisa 很高兴见到你 - 我也是
- Ryan. - Nice to meet you.
- 其实我叫Ryan - 很高兴认识你
- Pleasure. - Come here.
- 你好 - 快过来
I'll see you later,baby.
一会儿见 亲爱的
All right.
好的
So you and the wife aremaking another go of it.
你跟你妻子准备重新开始是吗?
Yeah.
是的
We went through a rough spotwhen i got back from iraq,
我从伊拉克回来以后 她跟我之间有一些不愉快的经历
And she was with thisother guy for a while.
那时她跟别人在一起
But put all that behind us,and so far,so good.
但现在已经没事了 目前为止一切都很好
Glad to hear it.
听到你这样太好了
Why is voight looking for you?
Voight找你干嘛?
Don't worry.
别紧张
He's just looking intoa shooting in my hood.
他在调查我家附近的一个枪击案
That's it.
仅此而已
Ambulance 61,engine 51,truck 81,squad 3.
61号救护车 51号消防车 81号云梯车 3号救援队
Accident at broad and wacker.
Broad街和Wacker街交汇处发生事故
Threecar accident with multiple victims.
三辆车相撞 多人受伤
I need two more ambulances.
我这里还需要2辆救护车支援
Copy that.
收到
Chief,we got the minivan.
头儿 我们处理这辆箱型车
Squad,check out the second car.
队长 你查看第二辆车
Capp!You grab the passenger.
Capp!你负责车里的人
Tony,clarke,you guys grab the pickup.
Tony和Clarke 你俩负责那辆皮卡
On it.
马上就去
Casey,we got two booster seats!
Casey 发现两个儿童座椅!
Check for kids.
找一下看有没有孩子
I'll get in to the driver.
我到车里去查看伤者
51,drop two lines and charge 'em.
51车的所有人 拉两条警戒线 封锁区域
- xxxx - I smell gas.
- 好的 - 我闻到汽油味了
Right away,chief.
头儿 马上就办
No kids!All clear in the back!
没有小孩!后面检查过了 没问题!
there.My name's matt.
进来了 我叫Matt
We're gonna get you outof here.Hang tight.
我们会救你出去的 撑住
Dawson,could use your help in the minivan.
Dawson 能到厢型车里来帮帮忙不?
On my way.Go help squad.
这就来 去支援
She's pinned in pretty good.
她被固定在座椅上了
- I need the small ram. - Got it.
- 我需要一个小型救生颚 - 知道了
- Hang on,guys. - I'm here.
- 撑住 伙计 - 我来了
we got two in the car.Both are bleeding.
我们这有两个伤者在车里 都在流血
Passenger's unconscious.
车里的人失去知觉了
bud,what the hell are you doing?
哥们 你他妈干嘛呢?
Get your foot off the pedal.
把脚拿开 别踩油门
Get your foot off the.
快把脚拿开
Capp,get over here!
Capp 把他拉出来!
- Get out. - That guy caused the whole thing.
- 出来 - 这一切都怪这个家伙
Was driving like a lunatic.
像个神经病一样开车
Let's get you checkedout in the ambo,come on.
我带你到救护车里检查一下 跟我来
Get something to knock him out.
给他打点什么 让他晕过去
Now,choot!
快点 Choot!
Let's go.
好了
Chest laceration.Shortness of breath.
胸口有撕裂伤 呼吸短促
Legs pinned,but seems pretty alert.
两腿被固定住了 但貌似是个好事
Just breathe nice and easy for us,okay?
尽量保持均匀呼吸 好吧?
We're gonna take good care of you.
我们会治好你的
- Casey? - Yep.
- Casey? - 在
I'm gonna put a ccollar on you.
我要给你上个颈圈
And then you'll be onyour way to the hospitalWhere you can see your family.
然后就送你去医院 你家人会去看你的
She'll be free in a sec.Almost ready?
她马上就能出去了 好了吗?
Almost.
可以了
Back board?
背板呢?
Dawson!
Dawson!
I'm good.
我没事
- You okay? - I'm good.
- 你还好吧? - 没事
Good.
那就好
Get back.
离远点
Hit it!
灭火!
As soon as the flames took over the car,
车子刚一着火
I was gonna jump in the back window myself.
我就准备从后窗跳进去
I do a lot of spelunking,so i'm good with diving into small spaces,
我经常搞洞穴探险 所以我能熟练的钻进狭小的空间
But i wasn't wearing my fire protective gear.
但我当时没穿防火服
Well,it's probably best if you.
是吗 那你最好还是...
Stayed outside?Yeah,that's what i figured.
呆在外面? 是啊 我也是这么觉得
My buddy that i go spelunking with,
总跟我一起搞洞穴探险的一个哥们
He throws these crazyparties on the weekend,and we always.
周末搞了个很疯狂的聚会 我们总是...
Choot?No offense,but i could reallyuse some quiet right now.
Choot?没别的意思 但我现在想安静会儿
My head's killing me.
我的头快要炸了
It's chout,actually.
应该是Chout才对
Lisa?I picked up some.
Lisa? 我带了点...
Baby.
亲爱的
What are you doing here?
你在这干嘛?
Well,heard about the two of you gettin' back together.
听说你们俩又在一起了
Wanted to offer myheartfelt congratulations.
想送个祝福给你们
But lisa and i stillhave unfinished business.
但Lisa跟我之间的事还没完
I loaned her some moneywhen we were together.
我们在一起的时候 她找我借了点钱
You're a real piece of work,hayes.
Hayes 你真够烦人的
I said i'd pay you back.
我说了 钱我会还给你的了
Get the hell out.
赶紧滚
I know all about you.
你的底细我都清楚
Lord knows i've heard enoughabout it from this one.
我从这娘们那里了解了很多事
I want my money.
我想要回我的钱
Hayes.
Hayes
I'm not gonna tell you again.Get out.
我不会多再说一遍 快滚
I swear to god i didn'tknow he was coming over.
我发誓 我真的不知道他会来
He just showed up.
他突然就出现了
But i'll take care of it.Don't.
但我以后会注意的 你别生气
That didn't go well.
看来情况不妙
That's how he always looks.
他平时就这样
Everything all right?
都还好吧?
It's fine.
没事
Who was that guy whowalked out right before.
比你先走出来的那家伙是谁
It's none of your business,capp.Drop it.
跟你无关 Capp 别问了
Hit it.
开车
Some cities have gone as far as to sue
有些城市到了一定阶段就会选择起诉
To stop cutbacks inessential emergency services.
以此来制止裁减应急服务机构冗员
Miami,omaha,stamford.
以前迈阿密 奥马哈 斯坦福都这么干过
You're thinking about a lawsuit?
你在考虑起诉?
Well,it's not a permanent solution,
虽然这不能彻底解决问题
But these closures thatmcleod is implementing,
但可以中止McLeod的计划
They're in breach of firefighters'contract with the city.
他们想破坏消防员与市里的合约
We could talk to sullivan,president of the union.
我们可以跟工会主席Sullivan对话
We get him to file an injunction against firehouse closures.
让他写提案要求终止关闭消防队
I don't know,chief.
头儿 我不确定
Greg sullivan is more about getting his picture taken than standing up
Greg Sullivan更关心自己出风头
For his fellow firefighters.
而不是为他的消防员朋友们出头
What?You don't think it's worth a try
怎么? 你觉得不该试一试吗?
consideringWe are kind offightin' for our lives here?
想一想 我们可是在 为我们自己的利益做努力
lieutenant,is shayserious about quitting 51?
副队 Shay调职的事当真?
She transferred to another house.
她已经转到其它消防站去了
So yeah,i'd say she's pretty serious.
我看应该是当真的
It's gonna be strangenot having her around.
没她在这里感觉怪怪的
I think this is just her feminine side kicking in,
依我看来应该是她女性那部分在作祟
Meaning temporary dramatics.
就是暂时的情绪波动
10 bucks says she's back here next shift.
10块钱 赌下一个轮班就回来了
Sergeant.
警长
Well,you didn't return my messages.Figured i'd pop by.
你没回我短信 我就顺道来了
Sorry about that.I'vebeen out on calls all day.
抱歉 一整天都在工作
Somewhere we can talk?
有地方可以聊一下?
Thanks.
好的
Insane kings have been trying to take over that turf again.
疯狂魔王那一伙人已经把 那片区域搅得天翻地覆了
Yeah,it's been pretty roughin my neighborhood lately.
我们社区确实最近不太安宁
I'll bet.
可不是
I noticed your brotherleon was in the kings.
我发现你弟弟Leon以前就是帮里的
He was.I'm proud to say he broke out of that life.
曾经是 很高兴他已经脱离了
He's on the straight path,going to community college now.
步入正轨 马上要上社区大学了
Well,congrats on that.
真是恭喜啊
Pretty tough getting out of the gang once you've jumped in.
混帮派 进去容易出来难啊
It's lucky thing his boss flaco was killed in that humboldt park fire.
他老大Flaco刚好死于Humboldt 公园火灾还真凑巧呀
And that little twist of fate made a big difference,i bet.
命运真是造化弄人呀
See,i was thinking maybe leon could help us.
我在想或许Leon能帮我们一下
Our best shot,maybe our only shot,
对我们来说是最好的方法 说是唯一的方法也不为过
is to put someone on the inside.
就是安插内应
Shooter's bound to startrunning his mouth at some point.
杀手终会浮出水面的
you want leon to go back into the gang?
你是想让Leon重回帮派去?
They'll sniff that out right away.They'll kill him.
他们一下就会发现 立马毙了他
Not if he plays it right.
如果做得好就不会
We need his help,joe,
我们需要他帮助 Joe
And i'm hoping we get it
我个人也希望这事能成
Because as long as i'm focusedon bringing down the kings,
因为我这人如果心思 全放在帮派这事上
I won't have time to take a closer look at
就没空去理会
What happened at that flaco fire.
Flaco是怎么被烧死的事了
Look. I don't know what you're talking about.
不知道你在说什么
As far as i remember,thatplace burned to the ground.
就我所知 那地方都被烧成灰烬了
You have a decision to make.
你好好考虑下吧
Come on in.
进来
It's weird not having shay here.
Shay不在怪怪的
Did you talk to her at all?
你跟她聊过了?
No. I left another message,though.
没 我又给她留了言
That suicide call's what started all this,and i.
这都怪那个自杀事件
I keep thinking that if i had just handled it differently,
我一直都在想要是我当时不那么做
Maybe she wouldn't have bailed on 51.
她就不会离开51号站了
You can't secondguess yourself.
事后假设没任何意义
Shay made the choice to switch houses.
Shay是自己做出调职的决定的
That's on her.
是她个人的意愿
But i was hard on her.
但是起因是我对她的态度
You're the p.i.c. Buck stops with you.
你是负责人 现场由你负责
When you're in charge of people,you.You can't always be best friends.
当你领导一群人时 不可能一直跟他们交朋友
Don't beat yourself up.
别自责了
Thanks.
谢谢
Not to get all schmaltzyor anything,but.
不是我太感性啊 但谢谢
Thanks for saving my life today too.
你今天救我一命
Yeah.
没事
You've done that forme like a million times in the last few months.
前几个月你不都救我几百次了
I've been thinking about it.
我很认真地考虑了
And the truth is.
扪心自问
I don't know where i'd be without you.
如果没有你 我不知道我会怎样
i had some questionsabout stocking the rig.
我对装备的整理有些疑问
You guys go through like ten times the amount of supplies i'm used to.
你们这的装备差不多 有我以前的十倍那么多
Yeah,sure.Okay,yeah.I can.i can.
好 没问题 我马上就去 马上
- Help me out? - Yeah.
- 帮我一把? - 当然
Cool.
太好了
Ready?Lift.
好了? 起
Okay,take it down.
好 平放
Good.
很好
We're goin' again.Mouch,sit down.
再来一次 Mouch 你休息
Herrmann,take my place.
Herrmann 你替我
Mills,otis.
Mills Otis
What the hell is goin' on?
这是咋了?
Looks like casey's got someserious steam to blow off.
看来Casey是精力过剩了
Extreme physical exertion,food deprivation.
挑战生理极限 剥夺食物
Are we in some kind of ciatraining program i'm unaware of?
我们这是在做中情局特训么?
Stop it.She'll be here any minute.
别吵了 她马上就会到
Who is this she you keep talking about?
你说的她是哪个她?
She's just a chef ata restaurant near here.
她是附近餐馆的厨师
This long a wait?
还要等多久啊?
Well,she'd better be a stripperchef popping out of a vat of pasta marinara.
她最好是位兼职脱衣舞娘厨师 从一大桶番茄肉酱里蹦出来闪亮登场
Maybe i oughta just throwsomething together really quick.
我是不是该先备好一些吃的
If she shows up,i'll get out of her way.
如果她出现 我自动消失
Go ahead.She ain't coming.
去吧 她不会来了
Everything go okay with voight?
Voight没找你茬吧?
Yeah.
没事
then why do you look like hell?
那你怎么愁眉苦脸的?
It's just been a rough day,that's all.
今天很不顺 没什么其它事
Have you ever worn a tux before?
你以前穿过晚礼服么?
- Prom. - Well,you rock it.
- 高中毕业舞会 - 你可是帅呆了
You are looking pretty damn good yourself.
今晚的你也非常美丽动人
Thank you.
谢谢
I think i got a plan ofwhat we're doing tonight.
今晚我俩的行程我已经计划好了
- do you? - Damn straight.
- 真的? - 尽请期待
God,not here.
天 看下场合
Champagne?
香槟?
thank you.
谢谢
- Cheers.
- 干杯
So who's this wheeler guy?
这个Wheeler是谁?
State senator.Rising star.
州议员  政治新星
I would love to run his next campaign.
我很想参与他的下次竞选
xxxxxxxxxxxx
你准备去毛序自荐?
I've been told i'm on his radar.
据我所知他有在考虑我
come on.I see him.
来吧 看到他了
I want to introduce you.
我想介绍你给他认识
Senator wheeler.
Wheeler议员
Isabella,good to see you.
Isabella 很高兴见到你
Good to see you too.
很高兴
I'd like to introduce youto my boyfriend,peter mills.
我想介绍我男朋友给你认识 Peter Mills
Very nice to meet you.
很高兴认识你
Yeah,same here.
我也是
Senator,i had some thoughts i wanted to runBy you when you have time.
议员先生 如果你有空 我有些想法想跟你聊聊
- Of course,anytime. - Perfect.
- 当然 都行啊 - 那太好了
Me and leon talked about it,and he doesn't want to do it.
我跟Leon谈过了 他不会去做的
So if you've got any dirtthat you got to dig up,go ahead.
如果你想找茬要挟我们 随便你们
That how you feel about it,leon?
这是你真实的想法 Leon?
Want to let your brotherroll the dice on this?
就让你哥说了算?
Sergeant?
警长?
Would you give us a second here?
能让我跟他们说两句么?
Leon getting himselfkilled doesn't help anybody.And if he.
让Leon去送死对谁都没好处 如果他
They took yvette offlife support an hour ago.
一小时前他们拆下了 Yvette的生命维持设备
She's gone.
她已经走了
I'm sorry,guys.
很抱歉
We're talking about the murderof a 10yearold girl here.
那可是杀害了10岁小女孩的凶手啊
You knew her.
你们都认识她
It's obvious that you both cared about her.
而且能看出来你们都很关心她
I want you to help usstop all of this,leon.
希望你能帮我们一把 Leon
Help us put away whoever did this.
帮助我们严惩真凶
We will be with you.
我们会全程协助你
We will be with him every step of the way.
每一步都会协助你
I promise you that.
我向你保证
So will you help us?
这样你能帮我们么?
xxxxxxxxxx
派对还不错吧?
no
很不错了
xxxxxxxxxxxx
那你接下来的计划是什么呢?
I gotta ask you a question.
我有个问题
the answer is yes.
回答是没问题
Did you bring me here tonight
你今晚邀请我来
Because you thoughthaving a black boyfriend would help you get the job?
是因为有个黑人男友 会帮你拿到这个工作么?
Absolutely not.
当然不是
It's just,you know,yesterday,we were reconnecting.
我这么问只是昨天我们才重新见面
Tonight,i'm your boyfriend.
今晚我就成了你的男友
It's. It's a quick promotion.
这进展也太快了
It seemed like the simplest way to introduce you,i guess.
我只是想这么介绍你最方便
Pete,i like you.That's why i invited you here tonight.
Pete 我喜欢你 这就是我今晚邀请你来的原因
Okay.
好吧
I'm gonna grab a cab home.
我打车回家
Thank you.
谢谢
Sullivan.
Sullivan
I have to make this quick,mcholland.
长话短说吧 McHolland
Have two meetings to get to.
还有两个会要开呢
I understand.I gotta get to work,too.
我懂 我也要上班
Did you have a chance to lookat chief boden's proposal?
你看过Boden队长的提案了吗?
I did.
看了
Then you know we've got a good case,
那你就知道我们赢面很大了
But the union has to spearhead it or we can't push it through.
但工会得作先锋 不然我们没法通过
Problem is i can't do it.
问题是我不能这么做
Why not?
为什么?
It'd be a pretty dumb move of me
我刚来一个月
To piss off state officials my first month into the job.
就得罪州政府官员太愚蠢了
You can understand that.
我想你也能懂
Let's be honest.This isn't my fight.It's 51's.
说实话 这不是我的斗争 这是51号消防站的
I was handed a lot of dirt about you during the election,
选举的过程中 我听说了不少你不光彩的事迹
And i kept it under wraps because i didn't think it was right for me
我一直保密
To personally benefit from airing it out.
因为我觉得通过曝光来给自己获利 不怎么光彩
But to protect my chief,and my brothers and sisters on the job,
但是为了保护我的长官 和一同工作的兄弟姐妹
I will shout it from the rooftops.
我会毫不留情公开的
I assume you're referring to my ex trying
你说的是我前任想
To chisel me for more child support.
朝我勒索更多抚养费的事
Yeah,that probably wouldhave done some damage,
也许那之前会有影响
But the election's over,pal.
不过现在选举结束了 老兄
Go ahead.Climb up on that rooftop.
去吧 大声说出来
No one will care,and you'll come across like a bitter loser.
没人会在乎 而人们会觉得你是个苦逼的输家
Lucy hofnagle.
Lucy Hofnagle
She's in my book club.
她跟我是同一个读书会的
You broke her heart,
你伤了她的心
Something your current wife would probably be surprised to discover.
你现任妻子可能对此会十分吃惊
no.
不是吧
Voight threatened to look into what happened with the flaco fire
Voight威胁说 如果Leon不去帮派卧底
If leon wouldn't go backinto the gang undercover.
他就会彻查Flaco的死
What?
什么?
But leon,he's gonna do it,lieutenant.
但是Leon答应了 副队
Our neighbor,this young girl.
我们邻居有个小女孩
She died.
死了
He wants to help,and i can't stop him.
他想帮忙 我没法阻止他
After everything i did to get him out,
我付出那么多努力想让他脱离帮派
Now he's going back in,and it was all for nothing.
他现在又要回去 一切都白费了
Getting him out ofthere wasn't for nothing.
让他脱离帮派并不是徒劳
It was.All right,itsteered that kid straight.
那把他引上了正途
You've done everything youcould for him,all right?
你做了你该做的 好吗?
Now,you have to trust that he'll make it outon his own this time.
现在你得相信 他这次靠自己能搞定
All right?
好吗?
Chout's back.
Chout来了
I am going to kill this guy if i have to sit nextto him one more second.
我再在他身边多待一秒 就会忍不住杀了他
You need to talk to shay.
你得跟Shay谈谈
I've tried,dawson.
我试过 Dawson
Maybe you should go by the apartment,talk to her.
也许你该来家里跟她聊聊
No,i've reached out.I've left messages.
不 我找了她 我留了言
She shuts me down every time.
她每次都无视我
She'd rather ride aroundwith that devon chick than talk to me.
她宁愿跟那个Devon妞一起 也不愿意跟我谈
I don't know what else i can do.
我不知道还能做什么
Ambulance 61,injury at 2909 north hudson.
61号救护车 Hudson北街2909号有人受伤
Let's rock and roll.
让我们摇起来
Thank god.This way.
谢天谢地 这边来
I heard someone coming in the back door.
我听见后门有人
I thought it was an intruder,
我以为有人入侵
So i went at him before i realized it was just my neighbor luis.
所以在我反映过来那只是邻居Luis 之前我就动手了
You went at him?
动手了?
Look,it's pulsating.
看 这东西在跳动
It's directly in the.
它直接插进了
Heart.
心脏里
My god.
天啊
If it moves much,we could lose him.
如果移动得太厉害 他可能会死
We have to stabilize it completely.
我们得完全稳定住它
Grab a twoinch tape.We gotta secure the fork.
拿个两英寸胶带 我们得固定住叉子
- Do you bake,ma'am? - I'm sorry?
- 你烤蛋糕吗 女士? - 什么?
I need a bundt cake pan,the kind with a.A hole in the center.
有那种中间有洞的圆环蛋糕盘吗?
Yeah,i. I got one of those.
我有一个
Chout,i can't do this without you.
Chout 我一个人做不来
Let's rock and roll.Come on.
来吧 我们摇起来
This should stop anythingfrom knocking into it
这能防止别的东西撞到它
Or sending it in any deeper.
或把它插得更深
Hold that there for me,nice and firm.
帮我扶着 稳住
Okay,let's get him on thebackboard nice and slow.
好 慢慢把他扶到背板上
Did you see how impressedthat attending was when he saw the setup?
你有没有看到那个主治大夫 看到那个装置时有多惊叹?
Yeah.
是啊
i got to ask.
我想问问
What happened with youand your old partner,shay?
你跟你以前的搭档Shay怎么了?
Sometimes partners go their separate ways.Happens.
有些时候搭档会分道扬镳 这很正常
Maybe she was intimidated.
也许她怕了
You gotta bring theagame to be your partner.
一流的人才能当你的搭档
You're.You're amazing.
你太棒了
Well,shay's pretty amazing too.
Shay也很棒
you know my buddyblair,the one i spelunk with?
我好朋友Blair 跟我一起探险的那个
His lake house party is this weekend.
在这周末会在湖滨别墅 举行派对
You and me,we should go.
我们去吧
Together.
一起去
Chout,you're a really nice guy,but the thing is.
Chout 你是个好人
I'm taken.
但我已经心有所属了
it's betty crocker.Those home ec.Classesfinally paid off,huh?
这不是Betty Crocker吗? 那些自学课程终于派上用场了 对吧?
Choot wants me totell your cake pan story on my next podcast.
Choot让我在播客上 讲述你用蛋糕盘的故事
Apparently,he's a big fan of the show.
很明显他是个大粉丝
- Sorry. - no problem.
- 借过 - 没事
Come on,let's go.
来吧 走吧
Change at the bar.We'relate for deliveries.
去酒吧再换 不然来不及送货了
You wanted to see me,chief?
你想见我 队长?
Yeah.
是的
I just got a call fromcommissioner's office.
我刚接到署长办公室的电话
An injunction against mcleodand her bosses is in the works.
针对McLeod和她上级的禁令 正在着手准备
Glad to hear it.
这是个好消息
It's just been really crazy.I'm sorry.
之前实在忙疯了 抱歉
You were never planningon coming,were you?
你根本没打算来 是吧?
I was ten when i met benny for the first time.
我第一次见Benny的时候 才十岁
He held me really tight,and said how sorry he was
他紧紧地抱着我 告诉我很抱歉
And how he was gonna be in my life.
还说他以后会在我的生命中 扮演什么样的角色
How i was his daughter.
说我是她的女儿
And i mean,i can't tell you how much that meant to me.
我说不出那对我意义 究竟有多重大
The next time i saw him was two weeks ago.
但等到下次见到他时 就是两周前了
I'm sorry he disappeared on you,katie.
我很抱歉他消失了 Katie
I'm really happy with my life right now,and i just.
我很满意现在的生活 我只是
I don't want to spend anymore of it
我不想再花时间
worryingAbout anothertrapdoor that might open,
等待一扇不知什么时候会开的门
So i just really hope thatyou can understand that.
我希望你能理解
I can.
我能
I'm not benny.
我不是Benny
I'm proud of you.
我为你骄傲
clarke!I thought you were heading home tonight.
Clarke! 我以为你今晚要回家
Decided it'd be better to come here.
我觉得来这里更好
All right.
好吧
Sometimes you need tostep away from a situation before it goes bad,
有时候在事情变得更坏之前 你得离开一下
You know what i mean?
你懂我的意思吗?
Yeah,sure.
懂
- I'm glad you came then. - Thanks.
- 我很高兴你来了 - 谢谢
I can't have you stepping out of line.
我不能让你做出出格的事
You got an ipa on tap?
有印第安淡啤吗?
Can you help this jarhead out?
来为这位大兵服务吧
Coming right up.
马上来
You drink too fast.
你喝太快了
Not fast enough.
还不够快
If i was drinking now,i'd drink fast too.
要我也会喝这么快
Because you're going back to russia.
因为你要回俄罗斯了
Yeah.
没错
I'm gonna miss you,joe cruz.
我会想你的 Joe Cruz
You know,maybe there's a solutionTo both our problems
也许咱俩的问题都有
besides drinking too fast.
除了喝酒之外的解决方法
I say you marry me.
我是说咱们结婚
Joe.You say this because you are sad.
Joe 你会这么说 是因为你很悲伤
In russian,this is koleno reaktsii ryvokl.
俄语里这就是koleno reaktsii ryvokl
I have no idea what those words mean.
我不知道你在说什么
I do know that i can't risk losing someone else i care about,
我只知道 我无法承受再失去一个在乎的人
And i think that we could have something really great together.
我觉得我们在一起会很棒
Marry me,zoya.
嫁给我 Zoya
Please.
求你了
Okay,joe.
好 Joe
Zoya and i are getting married!
我和Zoya要结婚了!
That's great!Good for you,buddy.
太棒了!真是太好了 老兄
let's have a drink to that.
干杯吧!
Damn right we should.
当然
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- 祝贺你 - 谢谢
Come here,you guys.
来吧 朋友们
Here you go.
给
congrats,buddy.
恭喜你 兄弟
That's really great.
这真是太棒了
They'll probably be married 50 years and have a bunch of kids,and.
他们应该会白头偕老 生一堆孩子
this is insanity.Mymom's gonna be ecstatic.
这太疯狂了 我妈妈一定高兴极了
I mean,over the moon,but this is insanity.
一定欣喜若狂 这太疯狂了
It's kind of.
确实
What the hell?
怎么回事?
Dude,the tv's gone.
老兄 电视没了
Shay?
Shay?
My viper helmet.
我的Viper头盔
are you okay?
你还好吗?
What the hell is going on?
这他妈怎么回事?
I gave devon a key.
我给了Devon一副钥匙
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync: YTET-天外飞砖
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: Grace S 片风 西瓜 校对: 狄克森 时间轴: 天外飞砖
chicago.fire.208.
风城烈焰 第二季 第8集